{
    "subject": "resource/Silent_Hill_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Psychological_horror_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of the film Silent Hill is psychological horror films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9008414149284363,
            "question": "What makes Silent Hill a memorable film within the psychological horror genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8319617509841919,
            "question": "What are some common elements found in psychological horror films like Silent Hill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8297821283340454,
            "question": "What are some potential reasons for the popularity of psychological horror films like Silent Hill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6301109194755554,
            "question": "Are there any psychological themes explored in Silent Hill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6118583083152771,
            "question": "What genre of film is Silent Hill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5929363369941711,
            "question": "Can you think of other films that share similarities with Silent Hill in terms of their horror approach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.578447163105011,
            "question": "What kind of horror does Silent Hill feature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5106959939002991,
            "question": "Would you describe Silent Hill as a film with jump scares?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44648477435112,
            "question": "How does Silent Hill explore the human psyche through its story and characters?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2190694659948349,
            "question": "How does Silent Hill use atmosphere to create fear?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of the film Silent Hill is psychological horror films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5087_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Silent Hill explore the human psyche through its story and characters?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5087_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Would you describe Silent Hill as a film with jump scares?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5087_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of horror does Silent Hill feature?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5087_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5087_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5087_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5087_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5087_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5087_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5087_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5087_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5087_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5087_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5087_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support this statement. For example, the text from `37.txt` and `104.txt` states that \"What truly sets Silent Hill apart is its emphasis on psychological horror\" and further elaborates on how the game delves into themes of guilt, trauma, and existential dread through its narrative and gameplay mechanics."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text heavily emphasizes the psychological horror elements present within the Silent Hill franchise, describing its focus on internal conflict, themes of guilt and trauma, and monstrous representations of protagonists' deepest fears.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}